Southern New England Telephone Company Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Subject Files, undated, 1879-1994
  - Transportation, undated, 1942 (Box 313:, Folder 3233)
  - Twain, Mark, 1891-1961 (Box 313:, Folder 3234)
  - Tyler, Morris Franklin, undated (Box 313:, Folder 3235)
  - Vail Medal, 1959-1996 (Box 313:, Folder 3236)
  - Van Sinderen, A. W., 1977-1984 (Box 313:, Folder 3237)
  - Wire Gang No. 31 Work Book, SNET, 1906 (Box 313:, Folder 3237A)
  - Woodbury Telephone Company - Woodbury Telephone Company Records, 1978-1979 (Box 313:, Folder 3238)
    see also: box 334-339
  - Women Employees, 1947-1978 (Box 313:, Folder 3239)
  - Yale, undated, 1878-1962 (Box 313:, Folder 3240)
  - Oversize
    - Anniversaries - 75th of SNET - Advertising and Publicity, 1953 (Box 314:, Folder 2984)
    - Centennial of SNET - Memorabilia, 1978 (Box 314:, Folder 2990)
    - Printed Material Advertisements, undated, 1880-1941 (Box 314:, Folder 3071)
    - Town Histories: Bridgeport, Bridgeport Life Newspaper, 1935 June 29 (Box 314:, Folder 3122)
    - Oversize Materials
      - Rates, 1883, 1892 (Box (cab):, Folder 3075)
      - Statistics - Exchanges and Stations, 1881-1960 (Box (cab):, Folder 3084)
- Series VII: Publications, undated, 1878-1998
  - Clippings
    - from Newspapers, 1878-1997 (Box 315:, Folder 3241)
      (includes advertisements)
    - Daily News, 1985 January - March (Box 315:, Folder 3242-44)
    - Daily News, 1985 March - 1986 May (Box 316:, Folder 3245-57)
    - Scrapbooks
      - Telephone, 1899 (Box 317:, Folder 3258)
      - General, 1910-1913 (Box 317:, Folder 3259)
      - General, 1912-1927 (Box 317:, Folder 3260)
      - General, 1913-1917 (Box 317:, Folder 3261)
      - General, 1913-1919 (Box 317:, Folder 3262)
      - General, 1913-1922 (Box 318:, Folder 3263)
      - Hartford Flood, 1936 (Box 318:, Folder 3264)
  - Material produced by SNET
    - The Adventures of the Yellow Pages at Home, 1937 (Box 319:, Folder 3265)
    - Bill Inserts
      - 1997-1998 (Box 319:, Folder 3267)
      - Beyond 1997-1998 (Box 319:, Folder 3268)
      - Telephone News (Gaps)
        - 1927 June - 1928 May (Box 319:, Folder 3269)
        - 1931 June - 1932 May (Box 319:, Folder 3270)
        - 1932 September - 1934 September (Box 319:, Folder 3271)
        - 1934 October - 1936 September (Box 319:, Folder 3272)
        - 1936 October - 1938 September (Box 319:, Folder 3273)
        - 1938 October - 1940 September (Box 319:, Folder 3274)
        - 1940 October - 1942 December (Box 319:, Folder 3275)
        - 1944 August/September - 1947 (Box 319:, Folder 3276)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 319:, Folder 3277)
        - 1950-1951 (Box 319:, Folder 3278)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 319:, Folder 3279)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 319:, Folder 3280)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 319:, Folder 3281)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 319:, Folder 3282)
        - 1960 (Box 319:, Folder 3283)
        - 1961 (Box 319:, Folder 3284)
        - 1962 (Box 319:, Folder 3285)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 319:, Folder 3286)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 319:, Folder 3287)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 319:, Folder 3288)
        - 1969-1970 (Box 319:, Folder 3289)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 319:, Folder 3290)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 319:, Folder 3291)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 319:, Folder 3292)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 319:, Folder 3293)
        - Telephone News (BOUND as SNET News)
          - 1926 June - 1928 May (Box 319:, Folder 3294)
          - 1928 June - 1930 May (Box 319:, Folder 3295)
          - 1930 June - 1932 June (Box 319:, Folder 3296)
          - 1932 September - 1934 September (Box 319:, Folder 3297)
          - 1934 October - 1936 September (Box 319:, Folder 3298)
          - 1936 October - 1938 September (Box 319:, Folder 3299)
          - 1938 July - 1939 December (Box 319:, Folder 3300)
          - 1940-1942 (Box 319:, Folder 3301)
          - 1943-1944 (Box 319:, Folder 3302)
          - 1945-1946 (Box 319:, Folder 3303)
          - 1947-1948 (Box 319:, Folder 3304)
          - 1949-1953 (Box 319:, Folder 3305)
          - 1954-1955 (Box 319:, Folder 3306)
          - 1956-1957 (Box 319:, Folder 3307)
          - 1958-1959 (Box 319:, Folder 3308)
          - 1960-1961 (Box 319:, Folder 3309)
          - 1962-1963 (Box 319:, Folder 3310)
          - 1964-1965 (Box 319:, Folder 3311)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 319:, Folder 3312)
          - 1968-1969 (Box 319:, Folder 3313)
          - 1970-1971 (Box 320:, Folder 3314)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 320:, Folder 3315)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 320:, Folder 3316)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 320:, Folder 3317)
          - 1978-1980 (Box 320:, Folder 3318)
          - 1982-1983, Note: changes to non-titled insert (Box 320:, Folder 3319)
          - 1984 (Box 320:, Folder 3320)
          - 1985-1986, Note: changes to SNET News in 1986 July (Box 320:, Folder 3321)
          - SNET News (BOUND)
            - 1987 (Box 320:, Folder 3322)
            - 1988 (Box 320:, Folder 3323)
            - 1989 (Box 320:, Folder 3324)
            - 1990 (Box 320:, Folder 3325)
            - 1991 (Box 320:, Folder 3326)
            - 1992 (Box 320:, Folder 3327)
            - 1993 (Box 320:, Folder 3328)
            - 1994 (Box 320:, Folder 3329)
            - 1995 (Box 320:, Folder 3330)
            - 1996 (Box 320:, Folder 3331)
          - Telephone News Microfiche Cards, 1926-1987; Note: includes SNET News (Box 320:, Folder 3332)
    - Cleaner & Greener: SNET's First Environmental Decade, 1982 (Box 318:, Folder 3334)
    - Connecticut Answers! Fights!, 1942 (Box 320:, Folder 3335)
    - Connecticut: I-SNET Introducing Connecticut's Information Super Highway, 1992 (Box 320:, Folder 3336)
    - Connecticut Locality List, 1967 October (Box 320:, Folder 3337)
    - Count on It, [1983?] (Box 320:, Folder 3338)
    - The Dial System in New Haven, 1928 (Box 320:, Folder 3339)
    - Directory Story, undated (Box 320:, Folder 3340)
    - Employee Library - Catalog of Books, undated, 1932-1937 (Box 320:, Folder 3341)
    - The Essentials of a Good Job to Have, undated (Box 320:, Folder 3342)
    - Extended Area Service - Questions and Answers for Employees, undated (Box 320:, Folder 3343)
    - Friendly Service, undated (Box 320:, Folder 3344)
    - FYI Executive Audio Information Program, undated (Box 320:, Folder 3344A)
    - Heroes: A Look at Black History in Connecticut, 1989 (Box 320:, Folder 3345)
    - Hurricane and Flood of September, 1938, 1939 (Box 320:, Folder 3346)
    - Introducing SNET Internet, 1995 (Box 320:, Folder 3347)
    - LINX, undated (Box 320:, Folder 3348)
    - Local Area Newsletters, 1988-90 (Box 320:, Folder 3349)
    - Network, 1980 (Box 320:, Folder 3350)
    - Our Rate Story, 1953 (Box 320:, Folder 3351)
    - Our Telephone Store, undated (Box 320:, Folder 3352)
    - Out of Town Telephone Rates from New Haven, undated (Box 320:, Folder 3353)
    - Pamphlets - About SNET, 1984-90 (Box 320:, Folder 3354)
    - Pamphlets - Telephones and Telephone Service, undated, 1983-1992 (Box 320:, Folder 3355)
    - Pioneering the Telephone in Connecticut (comic book for 75th Anniversary), 1953 (Box 320:, Folder 3356)
    - Programs Marketing Manager, 1962 (Box 320:, Folder 3356A)
    - Reprints about SNET, 1983 (Box 320:, Folder 3357)
    - The Road After 1984: The Impact of Technology on Society, Note: for full report see: Series V - Studies, Reports, and Plans) (Box 320:, Folder 3359)
    - Service and Equipment Manual, 1950 (Box 321:, Folder 3359A)
    - SNET News, 1986-1996; Note: see Bill Inserts, Telephone News, above
    - SONECOR Systems, 1983 (Box 321:, Folder 3360)
    - Southern New England Telephone Co. - The Perfect Telephone, 1892 (Box 321:, Folder 3361)
    - Special Olympics World Games Commemorative Program, 1995 (Box 321:, Folder 3362)
    - Stationary Standards, 1976 (Box 321:, Folder 3363)
    - Telephone Etiquette, 1905 (Box 321:, Folder 3364)
    - The Telephone in Connecticut from 1878 to the Present, 1969 (Box 321:, Folder 3365)
    - Telephone Service in Rural Connecticut, undated (Box 321:, Folder 3366)
    - TMS Telephone Maintenance Radio Service, 1974-77 (Box 321:, Folder 3367)
    - The Story of the Telephone Operator, undated (Box 321:, Folder 3368)
    - Vietnam Veterans Alliance For Understanding, 1990-Mar (Box 321:, Folder 3368A)
    - A Whale of a Story, 1954? (Box 321:, Folder 3369)
    - Why We do it and How, 1930 (Box 321:, Folder 3370)
    - World's Fair Program - The Southern New England Telephone Co., 1964 (Box 321:, Folder 3371)
    - You and Your Telephone: A Pamphlet on Good Telephone usage, undated (Box 321:, Folder 3372)
    - Your Dial Telephone, 1932 (Box 321:, Folder 3373)
  - Material Produced by Others
    - Alexander Graham Bell, 1973 (Box 321:, Folder 3374)
    - The American Telephone Journal, 1906 (Box 321:, Folder 3375)
    - Bell System Views on Communications Policy, 1975 (Box 321:, Folder 3376)
    - Bell Telephone Magazine - Anniversary Issue, vol.26 no.1, 1947 (Box 321:, Folder 3377)
    - Bell Telephone Magazine - Special Commemorative Issue no 3-4, 1983 (Box 321:, Folder 3378)
    - The Birth and Babyhood of the Telephone by Thomas A. Watson, 1934 (Box 321:, Folder 3378A)
    - The Brooklyn Manufacturer, 1897 February (Box 321:, Folder 3378B)
    - Bulletins of Current Decisions - AT&T Co.
      - 1940 June - December (Box 321:, Folder 3379)
      - 1941 January - May (Box 321:, Folder 3380)
      - 1941 June - December (Box 321:, Folder 3381)
      - 1942 (Box 321:, Folder 3382)
      - 1943 January - May (Box 321:, Folder 3383)
      - 1943 June - December (Box 321:, Folder 3384)
      - 1944 (Box 321:, Folder 3385)
    - Business Exchange Sales (Memorandum), 1932 August (Box 321:, Folder 3385A)
    - Committee on Regulatory Objectives and Procedures, 1970; (6 pamphlets) (Box 321:, Folder 3386)
    - Current Developments, 1954 July (Box 321:, Folder 3386A)
    - Electronic Switching - A “New” Brain for Communications, 1969 (Box 322:, Folder 3387)
    - Events in Telephone History, 1971 (Box 322:, Folder 3388)
    - Farmer's Open Forum, 1917 (Box 322:, Folder 3389)
    - General Pamphlets - Bell System, undated, 1936 (Box 322:, Folder 3390)
    - General Pamphlets - Bell System and Disasters, 1938-1975 (Box 322:, Folder 3391)
    - General Pamphlets - Overseas Service, undated, 1955 (Box 322:, Folder 3392)
    - General Pamphlets - Telephone, undated, 1971-1974 (Box 322:, Folder 3393)
    - General Pamphlets - Telephone Development, 1931-1976 (Box 322:, Folder 3394)
    - Great Books from Little Listings Grow (Bell Telephone Magazine reprint), 1951-1952 Winter (Box 322:, Folder 3395)
    - Introduction to the Bell System, 1975 (Box 322:, Folder 3396)
    - The Necessary Toy: The Telephone Comes to Chicago, 1975 (Box 322:, Folder 3397)
    - Notes From... Bell Systems Treasurers Conference, 1927 (Box 322:, Folder 3398)
    - Nutmeg Pioneer Vol. 10 no.3, 1963 August (Box 323:, Folder 3399)
    - Progress in Extending Bell Rural Telephone Service, 1946-1947 (Box 323:, Folder 3400)
    - A Quick Guide to the New Telecom Lingo, 1988 (Box 323:, Folder 3401)
    - Residence Market for Long Distance (Survey), 1955 (Box 323:, Folder 3401A)
    - The Shape of Bells to Come, 1983 (Box 323:, Folder 3402)
    - The Social Impact of the Telephone in America, 1979 (Box 323:, Folder 3403)
    - Telephone Almanac, 1928, 1930 (Box 323:, Folder 3404)
    - The Telephone Book 1876-1976, 1977 (Box 323:, Folder 3404A)
    - Telephone Catalog, [1930s?] (Box 323:, Folder 3404B)
    - Telephone Review, 1915 January, 1919 August, 1920 May, 1944 September (Box 323:, Folder 3405)
    - Telephone A Star (National Geographic), 1962-May (Box 323:, Folder 3405A)
    - TWX (Telephone Exchange Service) Directory, 1970 April (Box 323:, Folder 3405B)
    - Union Voice (Box 323:, Folder 3406)
      - 1949 June
      - 1967 January
      - 1969 January - December
    - The World's Telephones, 1975 (Box 323:, Folder 3407)
  - Periodicals, Note: the periodicals are listed here for reference purposes but are cataloged in the university online catalog.
  - A to Z Titles List
    - The Bulletin see Periodicals and Bound Periodicals, The Telephone Bulletin
    - City/Town Directories see Directories and Bound Directories
    - Connecticut Communications see Periodicals
    - Connecticut Statewide Directories see Directories
    - Connecticut Telephone Directories (statewide) see Bound Directories
    - Directories: see also Directories, Bound Directories
    - Management Topics see Bound Periodicals
    - New England Business Telephone Directory see Directories
    - News Briefs see Bound Periodicals, News In Brief
    - News In Brief see Bound Periodicals
    - News Briefs/News Flash see Bound Periodicals, News In Brief
    - News In Depth see Bound Periodicals
    - Official Directories see Directories
    - “Phone Books” see Directories, Bound Directories
    - Predecessor/Subsidiary Company Directories see Directories
    - Retired Employees Directory (SNET) see Directories
    - SNET Information Digest see Periodicals and Bound Periodicals
    - Telecommunications Insight see Periodicals
    - Telephone News see Periodicals and Series VII, Bill Inserts
    - Telephone Bulletin see Periodicals, Oversized Periodicals, Bound Periodicals and Oversized Bound Periodicals
    - Telephone Times see Oversized Bound Periodicals
    - Telling and Selling see Bound Periodicals
    - Yellow Page Hi-Lites see Periodicals
  - Periodicals (Boxed and Foldered)
    - The Bulletin, note: see The Telephone Bulletin (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Communications (gaps)
      - 1961 Fall
      - 1962 Spring, Fall
      - 1963 Spring, Summer, Winter
      - 1964 Spring - Winter
      - 1965 Spring - Winter
      - 1966 Spring - Winter
      - 1967 Spring, Fall
    - Management Topics, Note: see Bound Periodicals, Management Topics 1979-1980
    - News In Brief, Note: see Bound Periodicals, News In Brief 1940-1978
    - News Briefs, News In Brief, Note: see Bound Periodicals
    - News In Depth, Note: see Bound Periodicals, News In Depth 1977-1979
    - SNET Information Digest (gaps)
      - 1956-1967
      - 1968-1970, Note: see also Bound Periodicals SNET Information Digest 1955-1976
    - Telecommunications Insight, 1992 April - 1993 January
    - The Telephone News Vol. 1 No. 1 (copy), 1907 June
    - The Telephone Bulletin (gaps)
      - 1909 June Vol. 2
      - 1909-1910 Vol. 3
      - 1910-1911 Vol. 4
      - 1911-1912 Vol. 5
      - 1912-1913 Vol. 6
      - 1913-1914 Vol. 7
      - 1914-1915 Vol. 8
      - 1915-1916 Vol. 9
      - 1916-1917 Vol. 10
      - 1917-1918 Vol. 11
      - 1918-1919 Vol. 12
      - 1919-1920 Vol. 13
      - 1920-1921 Vol. 14
      - 1921-1922 Vol. 15
      - 1922-1923 Vol. 16 (Box 2)
      - 1923-1924 Vol. 17
      - 1924-1925 Vol. 18
      - 1925-1926 Vol. 19
      - 1926-1927 Vol. 20
      - 1927-1928 Vol. 21
      - 1928-1929 Vol. 22
      - 1929 Vol. 23
      - 1930 Vol. 24
      - 1931 Vol. 24, Note: see Oversized Periodicals for 1931-1946 Vol. 25-39
      - 1947
      - 1948
      - 1949
      - 1950
      - 1951
      - 1952 (Box 3)
      - 1953
      - 1954
      - 1955
      - 1956
      - 1957
      - 1958
      - 1959 (Box 3)
      - 1960
      - 1961
      - 1962
      - 1963
      - 1964
      - 1965 (Box 4)
      - 1966, 1968 March/April
      - changes to: The Bulletin
        - 1970
        - 1971
        - 1972
        - 1973
        - 1974
        - 1975
        - 1976
        - 1977, 1978
        - 1979, Note: see also Bound Periodicals, Oversized Periodicals, and Oversize Bound Periodicals, The Telephone Times
    - Telephone Times, Note: see Oversized Bound Periodicals Telephone Times 1961-1997
    - Telling and Selling, Note: see Bound Periodical Telling and Selling 1984-1985
    - Yellow Page Hi-Lites, 1958 July, 1959 May, 1973 May
  - Oversized Periodicals (Boxed and Foldered)
    - The Telephone Bulletin (Box 5)
      - 1931-1932 Vol. 25
      - 1932-1933 Vol. 26
      - 1933-1934 Vol. 27
      - 1934-1935 Vol. 28
      - 1935-1936 Vol. 29
      - 1936-1937 Vol. 30
      - 1937-1938 Vol. 31 (Box 6)
      - 1938-1939 Vol. 32
      - 1939-1940 Vol. 33
      - 1940-1941 Vol. 34
      - 1941-1942 Vol. 35
      - 1942-1943 Vol. 36-37
      - 1943-1944 Vol. 38
      - 1944 Vol. 39
      - 1945
      - 1946
  - Bound Periodicals, Note: located in Dodd Periodicals
    - Management Topics
      - 1979
      - 1980
      - 1981
      - 1982
    - News In Brief
      - 1940-1941
      - 1942-1943
      - 1944-1945
      - 1946-1947
      - 1948-1949
      - 1950-1951
      - 1952-1953
      - 1954
      - 1955
      - Changes to: News Briefs
        - 1957
        - 1958
        - 1959
        - 1960
        - Changes to: News Briefs/News Flash
          - 1961
          - Changes back to: News In Brief
            - 1962-1965
            - 1966-1967
            - 1968-1969
            - 1970-1971
            - 1972
            - 1973
            - 1974
            - 1975
            - 1976
            - 1977
            - 1978
    - News In Depth
      - 1977
      - 1978
      - 1977-1978
      - 1979
    - SNET Information Digest (bound as Information Digest)
      - 1955-1958
      - 1959-1963
      - 1964-1969
      - 1970-1971, Note: title changes to Information Digest
      - 1972-1973
      - 1974-1976
    - The Telephone Bulletin
      - 1907-1912 Vol. 1-5
      - 1912-1913 Vol. 6
      - 1913-1914 Vol. 7
      - 1914-1915 Vol. 8
      - 1915-1916 Vol. 9
      - 1916-1917 Vol. 10
      - 1917-1918 Vol. 11
      - 1918-1919 Vol. 12
      - 1919-1920 Vol. 13
      - 1920-1921 Vol. 14
      - 1921-1922 Vol. 15
      - 1922-1923 Vol. 16
      - 1923-1924 Vol. 17
      - 1924-1925 Vol. 18
      - 1925-1926 Vol. 19
      - 1926-1927 Vol. 20
      - 1927-1928 Vol. 21
      - 1928-1929 Vol. 22
      - 1929-1930 Vol. 23
      - 1930-1931 Vol. 24 (fragile)
      - 1931 Vol. 25, Note: see also Oversized Bound Periodicals The Telephone Bulletin 1932-1946
      - 1947
      - 1948
      - 1949
      - 1950
      - 1951
      - 1952
      - 1953
      - 1954
      - 1955
      - 1956
      - 1957
      - 1958
      - 1959
      - 1960
      - 1961
      - 1962
      - 1963
      - 1964
      - 1965
      - 1966
      - 1967
      - 1968
      - 1969
      - 1970
      - 1971
      - 1972
      - 1973
      - 1974
      - 1975
      - 1976
      - 1977-1979
    - Telling and Selling (2), 1929-1930
  - Oversized Bound Periodicals
    - The Telephone Bulletin
      - 1932-1934 Vol. 25-28
      - 1935-1937 Vol. 28-30
      - 1937-1943 Vol. 30-38, Note: volume bound as SNET Bulletin
      - 1941-1942
      - 1943-1944 Vol. 38
      - 1944-1945 Vol. 39
      - 1945-1946
    - Telephone Times
      - 1961-1962 Vol. I
      - 1962-1963 Vol. II
      - 1963-1964 Vol. III
      - 1964-1965 Vol. IV
      - 1965-1966 Vol. V
      - 1966-1967 Vol. VI
      - 1967-1968 Vol. VII
      - 1968-1969 Vol. VIII
      - 1970 Vol. IX
      - 1970-1971 Vol. X
      - 1971-1972 Vol. XI (2)
      - 1972-1973 Vol. XII, Note: bound as volume VII
      - 1973-1974 Vol. XIII
      - 1974-1975 Vol. XIV
      - 1975-1976 Vol. XV
      - 1976-1977 Vol. XVI
      - 1977-1978 Vol. XVII
      - 1979 Vol. XVIII
      - 1980 Vol. XIX
      - 1981 Vol. XX
      - 1982 Vol. XXI
  - Directories (Boxed and Foldered)
    - City/Town Directories, Note: see also Bound Directories, City/Town Directories (Box 7)
      - Bridgeport Division, 1890 January - October
      - Hartford Area List of Subscribers, 1882-1883
      - Waterbury Division, 1889 October
      - Windsor Locks, 1931 August
      - Winsted - Canaan, 1962-1963
    - Connecticut Statewide Directories, Note: see also Bound Directories, Connecticut Telephone Directories (statewide)
      - 1888 July
      - 1893 February
      - 1893 August
      - 1896 July
      - 1898 April
      - 1898 October
      - 1899 January
      - 1901
      - 1902 October
      - 1903 October
      - 1907 January
      - 1909 January
      - 1919 June
    - New England Business Telephone Directory, 1932-1933
    - Official Directories (SNET)
      - 1924 January
      - 1929 (2)
      - 1934 June
      - 1941 December
      - 1945 November
      - 1946 October (2)
      - 1947 August (2)
      - 1948 November
      - 1949 September (Box 8)
      - 1951-52
      - 1953
      - 1957
      - 1957 September (2)
      - 1958 September (2)
      - 1960 January
      - 1960 November
      - 1961 November
      - 1974 January
    - Official PBX Directory, SNET, 1924 January
    - Predecessor/Subsidiary Company Directories
      - Canaan Local Telephone Company, 1902 February
      - Connecticut Telephone Company Subscribers List, 1880-1881
      - Connecticut Telephone Company State Directory (reproduction), 1882
      - District Telephone and Automatic Signal Company (Hartford), 1879 June
      - New Haven District Telephone Company (1st one in the world), 1878; Note: Restricted, Fragile - Handle w/staff supervision only (Box 9)
      - New London Telephone Company, 1880 (Box 8)
      - Telephone Dispatch Company (Bridgeport), 1881 March
      - Western Union Telephone Exchange, [1879?]
    - Retired Employees Directory (SNET)
      - 1961
      - 1962
      - 1963
      - 1964
      - 1965
      - 1966
      - 1967
      - 1968
      - 1969
      - 1970
      - 1971
      - 1974
  - Bound Directories, Note: located in Dodd Periodicals
    - City/Town Directories
      - Ansonia - Derby
        - 1942-1944
        - 1945-1947
        - 1949-1951
        - 1952-1953
        - 1954-1957
        - 1958-1960
        - 1960-1962
      - Birmingham, 1891-1893
      - Bridgeport
        - 1889-1893
        - 1920-1921
        - 1921-1923
        - 1923-1925
        - 1925-1927
        - 1927-1928
        - 1929
        - 1930 (2)
        - 1931-1932
        - 1933-1935
        - 1936-1938
        - 1939-1940
        - 1941-1944
        - 1948
        - 1949
        - 1951
        - 1952-1953
        - 1954-1955
        - 1956-1957
        - 1958-1959
      - Bridgeport-Stratford, 1960-1962
      - Bristol
        - 1932-1944
        - 1945-1947
        - 1948-1951
        - 1952-1955
        - 1956-1957
        - 1958-1960
        - 1960-1962
      - Cheshire
        - 1954-1956
        - 1956-1957
      - Clinton
      - Clinton-Guilford-Madison
        - 1956-1957
        - 1958-1960
        - 1960-1962
      - Danbury
        - 1891-1893
        - 1932-1933
        - 1934-1937
        - 1938-1940
        - 1941-1944
        - 1945
        - 1947-1948
        - 1949-1951
        - 1952-1955
        - 1956-1957
        - 1958-1959
        - 1960-1962
      - Derby
        - 1932-1935
        - 1936-1941
      - Hartford
        - 1879
        - 1889-1893
        - 1920-1921
        - 1921-1923
        - 1923-1925
        - 1925-1926
        - 1926-1927
        - 1927-1928
        - 1929
        - 1930
        - 1931
        - 1932-1933
        - 1934-1935
        - 1938-1939
        - 1940-1941
        - 1942-1943
        - 1960-1962
      - Manchester
        - 1932-1937
        - 1938-1944
        - 1945-1948
        - 1949-1951
        - 1952-1954
      - Manchester - Rockville
        - 1955-1957
        - 1958-1959
        - 1960-1962
      - Meriden
        - 1890-1893
        - 1935-1938
        - 1939-1943
        - 1944
        - 1945-1946
        - 1947-1948
        - 1949-1950
        - 1952-1955
        - 1956-1957
        - 1958-1959
        - 1960-1962
      - Middletown
        - 1891-1993
        - 1936-1939
        - 1940-1944
        - 1945-1948
        - 1949-1951
        - 1954-1955
        - 1956-1957
        - 1958-1960
        - 1960-1961
      - Milford
        - 1947-1949
        - 1950-1951
        - 1952-1955
        - 1956-1957
        - 1958-1960
        - 1960-1962
      - New Britain
        - 1891-1893
        - 1932-1934
        - 1935-1937
        - 1938-1940